English

Open Menu Close Menu

 English

Open Menu Close Menu

**Privacy Policy**
==================

Welcome to our privacy policy, where you can find the details on how we process data, what service providers we use, and how we protect your privacy. Your personal information will be treated securely and confidentially in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations.

1. ### Data processing activities through Xayn

When you use our website, we receive information about you that may directly or indirectly identify you (“personal information” or “personal data”).

**What data we collect**

This website collects personal data to power our site analytics, including:

* Information about your browser, network, and device
    
* Web pages you visited prior to coming to this website
    
* Your IP address

This information may also include details about your use of this website, including:

* Clicks
    
* Internal links
    
* Pages visited
    
* Scrolling
    
* Searches
    
* Timestamps

We share this information with Squarespace, our website analytics provider, to learn about site traffic and activity. To learn more about what Squarespace does with visitor data, see section 12 of its [Privacy Policy](https://www.squarespace.com/privacy).

When you contact us via one of our contact forms, you will share:

* Your first and last name
    
* Your job title
    
* Your email address
    
* Your phone number
    
* Your country of residence
    
* The name of your company
    
* The size of your company
    
* The message you share with us

We share the information you share via our contact forms with Salesforce, a customer relationship management (CRM) platform, which we use to manage our sales and marketing activities. When you submit information through our contact form, we collect and store your data in Salesforce to facilitate communication and provide you with relevant information about our products and services. For more information on Salesforce's data protection and security practices, please refer to their [Privacy Policy](https://www.salesforce.com/eu/company/privacy/ "https://www.salesforce.com/eu/company/privacy/").

**Why we collect this data**

We may use this information in the following ways:

* To enhance the experience of using our website, services, and marketing activities
    
* To respond to your inquiries and provide you with information or services you request from us
    
* To send you marketing communications, such as newsletters and product updates, if you have consented to receive them
    
* To manage your access to the Xayn testing environment
    
* For any other purpose, we describe at the time we collect information
    
* For any reason you engage us
    
* For any other purpose with your consent

**Cookies**

This website uses cookies and similar technologies, which are small files or pieces of text that download to a device when a visitor accesses a website or app. For more information refer to our [Cookie Policy](https://www.xayn.com/cookie-policy).

**Your Rights**

As our users, you have the right to be informed about how your data is collected and used. You are entitled to know what data we collect about you, and how it is processed. You are entitled to correct and update any personal information about you, and to request this information be deleted. You may amend or remove your account information at any time, using the tools provided in your account control panel.

You are entitled to restrict or object to our use of your data while retaining the right to use your personal information for your own purposes. You have the right to opt out of data about you being used in decisions based solely on automated processing. If you would like to exercise your data rights under applicable laws, or if you believe your privacy rights have been violated, please contact us at [privacy@xayn.com](mailto:privacy@xayn.com?subject=Privacy%20Inquiry).  

**Limits of Our Policy**

This Privacy Policy only covers Xayn's own collecting and handling of data. We only work with partners, affiliates, and third-party providers whose privacy policies align with ours, however, we cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.

Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.

This privacy policy is provided by us, Xayn AG, c/o CMS Deutschland, EUREF-Campus 3, 10829 Berlin, GERMANY. The contact address is [privacy@xayn.com](mailto:privacy@xayn.com?subject=Privacy%20Inquiry) ([imprint](https://www.xayn.com/imprint)).    

**_‍_**

#### **2\. Social Media**

Like most other companies, we are dependent on social media profiles in order to distribute and promote our products. We are aware of the critique social media platforms face with regard to data privacy. Therefore, we decided not to access any of the analytics data the platform operators provide to us. For example, we are not interested in knowing any demographic information of the users clicking on Twitter links. We know that this might not be clever from a marketing perspective, but our decision should be seen in the light of our goal to provide privacy-preserving technologies.

This being said, we operate the following social media websites:

The operators of the social media platforms (e.g., LinkedIn) are involved in the operation of the websites just listed. They are also responsible (controllers) within the meaning of data protection law. We cannot influence the data processing carried out by the platform operators and are dependent on the information the respective providers give us. To the extent we can exert influence and have a part in determining data processing, we aim to ensure that the operators of the social media platforms treat the data in a manner appropriate to data protection. 

**Data processed by us**

The data you disclose using our social media pages, such as comments, videos, pictures, likes, public news, and so forth are published by the social media platform. We may comment on or delete content if this is necessary (e.g., in case it violates laws). In some cases, we share your content on our site (e.g., when you compliment us publicly) and communicate with you through social media platforms (e.g., when you contact us on such platforms). We use social media platforms for marketing purposes. The legal basis for all those processing activities is our legitimate interest in operating a social media profile and marketing our App ([Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/HTML/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN#d1e1888-1-1)).  If we process your personal data on the basis of our legitimate interests ([Art. 6 (1) lit. f) GDPR](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/HTML/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=EN#d1e1888-1-1)), you may object to the processing and use of your data. In this case, we will no longer use your data unless our interests prevail.

**Data processed by the operators of social media platforms**

Social media platform operators use web tracking methods. Web tracking can be performed regardless of whether you are logged in or registered with the social media platform. We cannot influence the web tracking methods of the social media platform and, for example, cannot switch such tracking off. We cannot rule out that the provider of the social media platform may use data, for example, to evaluate habits, personal relationships, preferences, etc. In this area of tracking, we have no influence on the processing of data by the platform operator.

Further information on data processing by the provider of the social media platform and further possibilities for objection can be found in the privacy policy of the operators:  

* LinkedIn: [https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)

We have entered into an agreement with LinkedIn Ireland Unlimited Company regarding joint responsibility for the processing of data (a Controller Addendum). This agreement determines which data processing activities we are responsible for when you visit our LinkedIn website and which are the responsibility of LinkedIn. You can view the agreement at: [https://legal.linkedin.com/pages-joint-controller-addendum](https://legal.linkedin.com/pages-joint-controller-addendum)

Regarding personal data processed by us through social media platforms, you have the same rights as mentioned in our main privacy policy in section 1 above.

This privacy policy is provided by us, Xayn AG, c/o CMS Deutschland, EUREF-Campus 3, 10829 Berlin, GERMANY, [privacy@xayn.com](mailto:privacy@xayn.com?subject=Privacy%20Inquiry) ([imprint](https://www.xayn.com/imprint)).  

**_‍_**

#### **3\. Change Log**

**Changes to This Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so please review it frequently. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our websites. If we materially change the ways in which we use or share personal information previously collected from you through our Services, we will notify you through our Services, by email, or other communication.

**COMPANY**

**GET IN TOUCH**

**LEGAL**

**DEVELOPERS**
